[
    {
        "question": "Defekt",
        "answer": "Viga"
    },
    {
        "question": "Talent",
        "answer": "Anne"
    },
    {
        "question": "Detail",
        "answer": "Üksikasi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Disain",
        "answer": "Kujundus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ansambel",
        "answer": "Bänd"
    },
    {
        "question": "Diversioon",
        "answer": "Õõnestustegevus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tumba",
        "answer": "Iste"
    },
    {
        "question": "Turgor",
        "answer": "Raku siserõhk"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sille",
        "answer": "Tugede vaheline kaugus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kalle",
        "answer": "Viltu asend"
    }
]
